Come on, spill it.
A government agency activated
Code Red for CHENES.
They are in Hong Kong?
They found us.
But the question remains,
who helped them escape?
I know a way
for them to escape to Hong Kong.
But you know what that means.
Mikoy will be branded
a traitor to the agency.
And you'll hunt him down.
I guess I must fix this myself.
Let's begin.
Chiara!
Giancarlo de Luca?
His name is Donatello Belladonna.
The Painter.
Let me handle this first, Chiara.
Let me take down Giancarlo.
I've already been trained
by Agent Alex at the agency.
Who?
Because in a real fight,
every part of the body is fair game.
Mikoy!
Sorry.
Stop!
Take my hand.
My arm's getting tired.
Of course not!
I don't trust you.
You might double-cross me.
Wow!
Chiara?
What's this? First-name basis? Why?
Are you close to my sweetheart?
Huh?
Chiara,
you found someone who's skilled in combat
and apparently skilled in romance too.
Or
perhaps he was forged by the strength
of your love for each other.
First of all,
I wasn't forged.
I'm Pinagpala.
And can you please move over there?
Back away from me.
Why are you even here?
Why are you so close?
Easy.
- Give us space!
- All right.
Easy there, mister.
As if we don't have history together.
We don't!
Are you high?
And seriously, you're our enemy.
So stop acting all buddy-buddy.
Right?
Ow!
What? Was I supposed to thank you?
I just had this done.
I want constant updates on her location.
Okay?
By the way, why didn't you go with her?
We're out of budget.
Or maybe you're just afraid
of getting jealous
when you see Agent Alex reunite
with her most beloved asset.
That's not true.
It's better that she
went there on her own.
Alone.
Really?
And my passport already expired.
I haven't renewed it yet.
There, you admitted it.
You wanted to go.
What if Agent Alex
manages to bring Mikoy back?
That's not happening.
Why not?
Because that fool is hopelessly in love.
I mean, he's head over heels
for Chiara Valtrovi.
And once you reach that level
of foolishness,
it's hard to come back from it.
I don't think Mikoy is planning
to come back to us soon.
Fool.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's just like an ant bite.
An ant bite?
More like a dinosaur bite.
All right.
This place should be secure.
It's a safehouse owned
by a friend from the Triad.
I thought it was safe.
Then why did you lock the door?
Fair enough.
Even antibacterial soap
kills only 99.9% of bacteria.
There's still that remaining 0.1%.
So you know what? You're right.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
Wow. You're something else, Mikoy.
You compared our situation to bacteria?
You said this place is protected
by the Triad, right?
Is that where you got the gun?
Yes, that's the only logical reason
how I got the firearm.
But why?
The Triad isn't a friend of the Concordat.
Well.
Chiara, you know I can be extremely
persuasive sometimes.
Wait, wait, hold on. I don't get it.
Why are you helping us?
Weren't you sent by that
La Morte Bianca thing
to kill Chiara and me?
Yes, that's correct.
I was sent here by La Morte Bianca.
But not to kill this little one.
Little one?
What happened? Are you okay?
I just got injured
during training earlier.
But I'm okay.
You don't look okay.
I told you to always be careful.
I'm the one who got hurt,
yet you're scolding me.
You're actually talking back?
I'm just worried.
Wow.
Your Tagalog is getting better.
Enough about me. Who did this to you?
Big Joe?
- He's big, but that's all.
- What should I do?
You're so stubborn!
But can I still trust you?
Chiara.
Well, I was wondering why
La Morte Bianca sent you.
Or maybe she actually wants to know
if I can actually kill this ugly person.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! Foul!
This face is movie-star material.
And she'll kill you?
Because before she even finds out,
I may be far, far away
in Davao or Mindanao
or maybe in… South Africa.
Doing the tango or salsa.
At least you have a Plan B.
Yes.
Because I don't intend to kill
your stupid boyfriend here.
Exactly!
What's with all the "stupid"?
Okay, now you're going too far.
You know, you've been at it
for a while now.
You've been taking shots at me
this whole time.
For your information, I'm not ugly.
They say I look like Enrique Gil.
If you're Enrique Gil,
then I'm Brad Pitt.
- Impossible, right?
- Woah!
- Brad Pitt, really?
- Yes!
If you're Enrique Gil,
- you're…
- You're…
Stop!
Both of you, please!
And you, I know you.
Why do you keep saying ugly things?
You only say that
when you know something is up.
Chiara? Mikoy?
You and Mikoy still haven't seen
what La Morte Bianca
is capable of doing.
But we need to go now. Let's go.
Chiara?
Don't ignore what I told you
about La Morte Bianca.
I'm not ignoring it.
I know she's really dangerous,
but I'm also dangerous,
and I know Mikoy and I can handle this.
Right, sweetheart?
But seriously,
thank you for the warning.
I really appreciate it.
Do you have an exit plan?
Stop. I'll do it.
Give that to me.
Just move over there.
What are you doing?
I'm fine. I can do it.
You're clearly struggling to carry that!
Okay! Sorry! Sorry, sir! Sorry, sir.
Are these for delivery?
I'll just put these at the stall,
so they can see them right away.
I'll do it!
Why are you so sweet?
You don't want me to get tired, huh?
In your dreams!
I just want to finish this quickly,
so you can go home.
You want me to go home right away?
What a waste!
I still have a valuable update
about your brother.
Someone might hear you.
Lower your voice.
Relax!
Earlier, you wanted me gone, now…
you're holding me?
You, huh.
No!
Go home already!
Mom and Dad are coming back.
The store is close by.
Okay!
I get it! You don't need help!
But…
don't you really want to know
the update about your brother?
Okay.
Silence means yes.
All right. I'll just go home.
Okay! Okay! Okay!
You're winning.
Tell me the update about Mikoy.
Here goes.
Look at our boy there.
I've never seen him like that before.
Look. Look at those moves.
The way he's pressing his lips
to Sofie's ear, right?
Like…
Just like us when we were younger.
You only liked me
because I'm sweet, right?
You're always fooling around!
Come on.
Wait a second.
Why would I tell you?
It's okay. I still have a spare.
What are you talking about? What spare?
Nothing.
Here.
What do you call a man who has no balls
even if he has a spare?
- What?
- Mikoy!
- Okay, okay, okay.
You two are having fun, huh?
I wish we could stay longer
so you could bond some more,
but we don't have any time left.
Hey, dear.
You're still here.
So you really committed
to your stop-for-the-day plan, huh?
Of course, Auntie.
You know, it's so boring at the resort,
so I just stayed here
to spend time with Angelito.
Wait a minute.
Don't you have company?
What's the trend these days in your town?
Is this solo travel?
Oh, no, Auntie. I have company.
Actually, he's on his way here.
He said he'll text me when he arrives.
Speaking of!
Dad, sir!
Hey.
I'll see you again, Giancarlo De Luca.
Don't call me that! My name is Donatello!
Oh, Donatello!
All right, say hi
to Master Splinter for me,
and Raphael, Leonardo, and Michelangelo.
Okay, happy now
with your Ninja Turtle jokes?
- I'm happy for you. Happy for you, boy.
- Kind of.
Okay, okay.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
Don't move!
Put your hands up!
Agent Alex.
I missed you.
I said, hands up.
- All of you!
- Okay!
Here we go!
And don't try to do anything stupid,
because I won't hesitate
to pull the trigger.
Good afternoon, Mario, Tess.
Thank you for letting Sofie
stay here for a while.
Wait.
You look very familiar.
So familiar.
Maybe because you look like your cake
when it's burnt.
No! Wait a minute!
Oh my!
Bertong Butete!
Who's Butete?
Your father.
He looks like a tadpole.
Oh, Mario!
You know,
don't pay too much attention
to my husband.
He's a joker!
Surprised?
I know the language
because Italian was my elective
in college.
I've also read Inferno, Purgatorio,
and Paradiso,
by Dante Alighieri, for my thesis work.
Excellent! You know Divine Comedy.
Funny, isn't it?
Even though it's called Divine Comedy,
it's not actually funny.
Are we done reminiscing
about our literature courses?
Come on. It's like
I'm the third wheel here.
- Aren't we friends?
- Back off!
It's been a long time since we last met.
Get Sofie inside the house.
It's hot outside.
Sofie, come with me!
You two.
You better be sitting with each other.
We'll have a peaceful meal later.
Okay?
Talk to your husband.
He started it.
He looks like Minecraft Steve anyway.
See? He started again.
These two are at it again.
Follow me. Come on!
You look like Steve Martin.
Friends?
We're not friends, Mikoy.
Because a real friend
doesn't disappear without a word.
A real friend
doesn't leave you hanging.
That sounded personal.
Wow!
How about--
My God! Agent Sianong!
If you just wanted updates
about Agent Alex,
you should've teleported to Hong Kong.
That's harsh.
You're so grumpy.
I just wanted to know
if there's any update on Alex.
Maybe we can talk about this?
I'll explain everything.
Mikoy, you'd better do that.
Shut up!
Or I'll have you shot.
I'm sorry.
I mean, you're the girlfriend,
and she is the…
ex-girlfriend, correct?
What exactly are you going to explain?
That this is for the greater good
of the agency?
For our countrymen?
Mikoy, you ran away.
And you betrayed the cause.
You can't do anything here.
You have no jurisdiction here,
so why don't you just let us leave
because my arms are getting tired.
You are a Moraviano.
And Mikoy has an ex parte
warrant of arrest.
And I can shoot all of you
right here if I want to.
And this guy right here,
who looks like Giancarlo,
he's evil to the core.
So I'm doing the world a favor
by eliminating him.
And if you think about it,
the world will be a better place
without all of you.
What if Alex
is already sending you a distress call,
but because you're so busy
with your laptop and four phones,
you don't even notice it?
Because that's how it goes, right?
That's how it is in movies and TV dramas.
When the hero is in danger,
they call their contact person, right?
But then that contact person
gets interrupted by another call
or conversation.
Or something suddenly falls.
Or their phone is on silent.
Or the battery is dead.
Dara,
I just want to make sure Alex is safe.
That's all.
Point taken.
But this isn't a movie.
It was just an example.
I understand why you're worried about her,
because of your
one-sided feelings for her.
Wow, you're really pushing
the one-sided thing.
Okay.
Then do it.
Shoot us.
Sweetheart.
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
Shoot us from that moral
high ground you're standing on.
I thought I had your back
when it comes to Alex?
Yes.
I'm Team SiaLex
or Asiong.
My point is,
Agent Alex is a grown woman.
And if she needs our help,
she will definitely call us.
Please, please. Time out first.
Can we?
Let's all relax for a moment.
Okay?
Chiara, sweetheart, I'm sorry, but please.
Don't say anything yet, okay?
Let me do the explaining first, okay?
Alex, believe me.
I didn't betray the agency, okay?
And Chiara
is no longer with the Moravianos.
Then what is she?
Something like that.
Why?
Do you think I would lie to you?
Stay there.
Don't you want to fight fairly?
I don't have the gun.
Gosh, the electricity is gone.
Don't worry. The generator will work soon.
See. Thank you.
Sorry.
Alex! What are you doing?
Chiara? Chiara…